You might win an extra item!
I am strongly considering holding
a Dungeon Goddess Grand Prix.
Fine, but you're too close!
What the?
Back off there, Munami!
Sorry, sorry, sorry.
So hear me out.
With all the new refugees in the
village, the populations exploded.
I thought we should do something to
build strong relationships with them.
And then it hit me!
Why don't we hold a huge festival
and invite the entire town?
That led me to another idea.
I call it the Dungeon Goddess Grand Prix.
That's a good idea.
The eating contest we
held was a big success,
and this will serve as a
diversion, a much needed one.
Might be eat, not ice. Yeah, right?
I am going to need your
help to pull it off, Boxo.
I'll pay you one, no, two gold coins.
You see, I was thinking
that for the grand prize,
we could reward the champion with
50 of their favorite products?
from you free of charge.
What do you think?
At that point, I'd still
finish way up in the black.
There's no reason to refuse.
Hello there.
Thank you so much, Boxo.
You're the real MVP.
The Dungeon Goddess Grand Prix?
Shirley will be a top contender.
Oh, she surely will.
She has the looks, and she's used
to getting public attention, too.
What about you?
You're talking like you won't compete.
But you will if I have a say in it.
There is no way I'm competing.
I don't want to either.
I'm way too shy. Oh.
What if I threw in a week's worth
of free meals to sweeten the deal?
That does sound nice.
Well, I'm a no no matter what you say.
Aw, don't you wanna see what
these girls can do, Boxo?
What?
Now you're putting this on me?
That's not cool, man.
What's the right way to respond?
Should I say yes or no?
Seems like the kind of situation
where I'm screwed either way.
Think, man, think.
Too bad.
There, that's vague enough
to be taken either way.
Too bad?
Does that mean yes or no?
Yeah, be more specific, Boxo.
But how?
Fine, guess it's not good to be too pushy.
But consider this, girls.
If Shirley wins, she'll
get 50 items from Boxo.
I'm so overcome with emotion.
I might just grab Boxo
and give him a passionate
kiss right on the glass of his front side.
Or so she was saying.
But you two are not in. Got it.
Yes?
What is it, my dear sweet llamas?
I...
I guess I will enter the Dungeon
Goddess Grand Prix after all!
Oh, so Lamas has decided to enter.
You are really popular
around here, you know,
so that could make you a top contender.
Munami's enjoying this.
What about you, Hulemy?
Not that you have to feel
pressured or anything.
Uh, well, I...
Evil.
Ugh, fine, I'll enter, I guess. Huh?
Really?
Well, yes, because lately I've been
developing a magic item of attraction.
Entering could be useful for that process.
You know, for research purposes.
So then the both of you
are participating, huh?
Things have taken an interesting turn.
Yeesh.
Who's this sleazebag and what
has she done with Moon Ami?
I bet that bit about
Shirley was a lie, too.
But hey, if they're both entering,
they've got my full support.
On the outside, I'm just a big metal box.
But inside, I've still got a human soul.
In this new world of
wonders, I travel to and fro!
On the back of my super
strong partner, Lamas.
The name's Boxo.
Hello there?
That means yes, by the way.
Thank you.
Form change!
Oh, I love a festival.
There's been so much fighting lately.
This will be a nice change of pace.
I'll be there for sure.
Yeah, looking forward to it.
Says here it takes place in one week.
This looks like oodles of fun.
And rebuilding's going well.
Therefore, I feel it's only right that my
company should contribute to the cause.
I'm planning on taking
part in the Grand Prix.
Festivals like this really
are always so much fun.
And I want to contribute to do
the Clear Flow Locals proud.
Whoa, she won't be easy
to beat by any stretch.
Although I'd like to give my
two the upper hand somehow.
Do I have some product that
could help them win this thing?
Welcome to the How to Win the Dungeon
Goddess Grand Prix emergency meeting.
Thanks for coming.
Let's do this.
I'm gonna get that Voxo gift
certificate no matter what.
Let's bake this, cookie girls.
It seems there will be
quite a few contestants.
So these three have
decided to join forces.
All right, now let's talk logistics here.
First, each contestant
will introduce herself.
The attire for that round
is everyday clothing.
But we should still put
a lot of energy into it.
Mm-hmm. Well, naturally.
Next, we show off special skills,
but the assignment is twofold.
We have to demonstrate our skill
and appeal at the same time,
and we can wear whatever we like.
Special skills?
That's archery for me.
And, um, I guess I could pick
up some really heavy stuff.
I could show off some of my inventions.
But what about... clothes?
There's the rub.
All I have besides this is my
pajamas and boring casual stuff.
Oh, same here.
Yeah, I've never given much
thought to what I wear.
This is such a sad conversation.
What if we just made a few
slight alterations to the
clothes we're wearing now to
make them show a bit more skin?
Ooh, yeah, I like that idea.
Please, get a grip.
Do you think you can beat Shirley
when it comes to showing skin?
I can't beat that!
In my personal opinion, they have a shot
if they compete in terms of natural beauty.
But I think it'd be best
not to expose too much.
Well, there's a shop here
in town that sells fabric.
And I think there's still
time for me to make something.
Shui, you can make clothes by hand?
The kids at the orphanage
have always liked them,
Finding quality children's clothing in the
dungeon can be a real pain in the neck.
Then we just have to come
up with some good designs.
But don't ask me, I don't
think I'd be good at that.
Yeah, I have no idea how to
do any of that stuff either.
I'm good at children's clothes,
but I wouldn't know where to begin
with dressy outfits for adults.
Boxo, why'd you suddenly change shape?
What is that?
There are some very pretty
pictures in these books.
They're wearing clothes I've never seen.
This outfit's so cute!
Oh, yeah, this sort of
thing could work. Uh-huh.
Ooh, look, this is cute, too.
Is this what they wear
in the world box-os from?
Wow, amazing!
Ooh, I like this look.
This looks great!
That would work on me.
That's lovely.
Ooh, I like this.
I had a feeling they'd lose
themselves in this sort of thing.
Oh, that one just screams cute.
How about this one?
Wow. Yeah.
Wow, good work.
Glad we have some kind of plan.
I'll get going right away on our
wardrobe for the competition.
Thanks, Shui.
And we'll think up an idea for
your archery demonstration.
We've been through a lot lately, so
I'm just glad they're having fun.
As for what kind of outfits they've settled
on, seems I'll find out on the day of.
Hip, hip, hooray!
I'll have to see if I can come
up with some way to help, too.
The day has finally come for the Dungeon
Goddess Grand Prix, or DGGP for short.
Clear for Low Lake Stratum's
festivals are amazing!
I've never had this much
fun in my whole family!
Good morning, Radies!
Oh, hi!
Good morning, Shui!
Hey!
I got no sleep, but I managed
to finish the outfits.
Shui must have been up all night sewing!
You poor thing!
But like we agreed, if any of the three
of us wins, we'll give the prize to you!
Yeah.
Truth be told, I don't see myself winning.
But if I manage to pull
it off, it's yours.
I appreciate it.
Well, Boxo, make some
noise, okay? Psst! Eat you!
Aw, crap!
I can't even see the stage from here!
And it'd be too much to move using the
cardboard vending machine and balloon combo.
Boxo, this is perfect
weather for a festival, eh?
Oh, but you can't see crap from there.
How about I move you somewhere
with better visibility?
Does that sound good?
Thank you very much!
Director Bear coming in clutch.
Oh, you gotta be kidding me.
Oh, Boxo's here too!
I've sure been looking forward to today.
Too much, actually.
In fact, I've got dark
circles under my eyes.
I see Director Dark is as
talkative as ever, isn't he?
Speaking of talkative, you'll never
believe what happened to me yesterday.
We've been working feverishly
to learn clear flow strategy.
Director Dark on my left,
Director Labyrinth on my right.
Worst surround sound ever.
Would you two chatterboxes
mind giving it a rest, please?
We'll be starting soon.
Your judges and I want you both
to take that rule seriously.
Sorry.
Heard and understood.
I hear you, big guy.
I promise to give it my all.
Whew. Thank goodness.
But wait, what am I doing here?
I figured I would invite
you to be a judge too, Boxo.
Director Origin was originally
supposed to be on the panel,
but she had to back out
for personal reasons.
And so Boxo got appointed instead?
I trust you'll be fair about it
even with your friends competing.
I'm happy to know he has confidence
in me, but now I have to be a judge?
That's a big responsibility.
Hello, everyone.
We appreciate you being
such a patient crowd.
And now,
the first installment of the Clear Flow
Lake Stratum Dungeon Goddess Grand Prix.
Who's the best girl, folks?
Now, let's go ahead and
meet our participants.
First up, to start us off right,
it's Akui from the Exchange House.
The only thing I'm after
is that grand prize.
Now, as you all know, nothing's
better than free stuff.
No strings attached is
the best deal there is.
Next is Thea, this lovely
lady from the item shop.
It turns out she was secretly very
popular among our male hunters.
But I hear there's been
lots of weeping and moaning
ever since she started
going out with Karyos.
Um, I promise to do the very best I can.
She's so cute!
Moving along, from the band of gluttons,
she's quick on her paws
and has a big appetite.
Here's Suco!
I just want to win and get all the
fried chicken that a girl could want!
You got this!
Number four!
She just entered yesterday,
which was a last-minute surprise.
It's Director Origin!
You look lovely, Director Origin!
Don't forget to smile!
I know, you can do it!
Whoa, it looks the tail scaring!
I don't know what you
expected considering she only
entered the competition because
of your relentless bullying.
I have no idea what you're talking about.
Oh, so that's why they needed
me to step in and be a judge.
This fine stratum is taking
good care of my residents.
To show my gratitude, I thought I'd enter
the competition and liven things up.
Direction!
And now, our fifth entrance.
She's also donated the
prize for this Grand Prix.
It's our very own girl boss, Stuari.
I'm here today to kick
butt and win first place.
Let's make this a great contest.
Number six, she's yet
another adorable entrant.
It's Kiku Yu.
I'll do my best.
Also, don't forget about all the fresh
vegetables I've got for sale over there.
All right, does everyone
have a favorite girl so far?
Well, hold your horses, because there
are still some you've yet to see.
Number seven, it's our hunter with
a stomach of steel, Shoo-Wing!
When I win, I'm gonna eat and
eat and eat until I explode!
We're down to the final three.
I wonder, who could our
next challenger be now?
Munami's starting to sound
like this is a prize fight!
Our brilliant magic
item engineer, Hulamain!
Hey, girl, you feeling pumped?
I am here, and that's enough.
Now, for our penultimate powerhouse,
This girl's a favorite to win!
Nothing slows down this super strong lady!
It's Llamas the Hunter!
Boxo!
I promise to give it my best shot!
Huh?
I didn't know Llamas was so popular.
But the crowd is going crazy for her!
And at last, it's time
for our final contestant!
Word on the street is
she's the favorite to win!
It's the moment you've
all been waiting for!
Give it up for Shirley!
Everyone, deep breath. Ready?
Now scream for me!
What's with this cheering?
It's on another level.
Will we be able to make up the
difference in later events?
Okay, ladies and gentlemen, let's
have another big round of applause!
Sure enough, Shirley's
the favorite to win.
Now we'll take a quick break
so the ladies can get changed.
But don't go far, because the special
skill demonstrations are up next.
Boxo, we need you for just a few seconds.
Sorry, it won't take long, promise.
What the heck is going on?
We probably don't...
No, we don't stand a
chance against Shirley,
but there's nothing that we can
do about it all by ourselves.
Look, we know that this is
asking you for a great deal,
but do you carry any products
that could make us more appealing?
Anything, please.
It's not like there are no options,
but we don't have time to do
this for all three of them.
I have a plan, but not enough.
You have an idea, but there's
not enough of something?
Like tools? Too bad.
Then is there not enough time?
Hello there.
Does that mean there's not enough time to
apply whatever it is to all three of us?
Hello there.
If that's it, then you
two should do it, not me.
After all, if either of you wins it,
I will still get the prize regardless.
Um, Shui, are you sure?
Of course I am.
You have your heart set on taking
first place way more than I do.
Mm-hmm. It's a deal. Thanks, Chewie.
Loxo, please, I'll do
anything to win anything!
I'm not confident, to be
honest, but I'll do what I can.
Form change!
A cosmetics vending machine!
What is this thing?
Ever since the three of
them decided to enter,
I have been reading fashion
magazines at night and practicing my
makeup skills to figure out what
looks people will like the best.
But make no mistake,
I bought all this stuff in the
name of my vending machine fandom.
Now, it's time to make these
two shine with my new skills.
Voxo's new vending machine power!
Makeup!
Bobso!
Ladies and gentlemen, thanks
for your patience today!
But it's time for the
special skills demonstration.
First up, number one, Akkui!
Take it away, girly!
High-speed coin sorting,
gold, silver, and copper.
Gold, copper, silver,
silver, copper, gold, gold!
Secret Rite, mixing a high mega potion!
Woo-hoo!
Speed eating!
Thanks for the food!
Way to go!
Here we go, boys!
So I and Kiko, you didn't
really do anything themselves.
Next, it's Shui's turn, finally.
How's she gonna dress, and what
kind of archery will she do?
Huh?
She's wearing a gym outfit?
That would've been my very last guess.
That outfit looks easy to move around in.
I've never seen that outfit before,
but it kinda seems just right.
Yes, it's hard to put my paw on it,
but something about that getup
really does draw the eye.
I think this might be the
best crowd response so far.
Now, moving on.
Pulumi and Llamas are appearing
as a team of two today.
Show us what you can do, girls.
Pulumi,
I never thought you'd take this approach,
and I'm surprised by how
well it works for you.
Llamas pulled off the blazer look.
This is, this is undeniably super cute.
It seems Hulemy is going to
unveil her new magic item.
Let's see what it is.
Okay, it's ready.
Activate.
Woo-hoo!
Now we lift!
No, don't!
Great.
Oh, no, no! I'm coming!
They got the crowd going the most.
And I'd like to think that the
outfits and makeup helped too.
Now the moment you've all been
waiting for, our final entry.
Mom, do I really have to read this?
I beg your pardon, everyone.
I do apologize, but...
Shirley has fallen ill and we'll
have to withdraw from the running!
No, what happened?
I hope she's okay.
I never imagined Shirley would drop out.
Now there's really no
telling who will win.
I guess we can only wait for the result.
I can't wait to see who wins.
It's just all so exciting.
Huh? Shirley?
Oh, too bad.
Yes, but I am better now.
It is too bad that I had to
withdraw partway through.
Uh-huh.
Thank you for the drink.
It's odd, but she seems
healthy enough to me.
What if...
I'll hold a little arm.
You be the judge.
Interesting.
This is just speculation.
But maybe Shirley only ever
said she was going to be
in the contest to get people
more excited about it.
Thank you very much.
Don't mention it.
Ah, voting has officially ended.
All we can do now is wait for the result.
Heavy doesn't care about
anything but shoes,
so I wonder if he really had
any interest in this at all.
Proveeked first place.
Well, let's see.
Personally,
I think Director Origins'
bright red boots are
stunning enough to win first place
on their own. Too bad! It's true.
Heavy never wavers.
Ladies and gents, once again,
thank you for being so patient.
But it is finally time
to announce the winner.
Oh, here it comes.
Now, let's find out who our champion is.
The honorable winner of the Clear Flow Lake
Stratum Dungeon Goddess Grand Prix is...
Unvelope, please.
She's perky, but don't forget
her super strength, folks.
It's Lamas!
You did it, Lamas!
I really did it, Boxxo!
And now we present the
champion, Lamas, with her prize.
Lamas, you win 50 meal tickets
from your favorite guy, Boxxo!
And this totally gorgeous magic item
courtesy of Suorries Corporation.
Those boots, finally.
I finally found them.
What does he mean?
Is there something up with those boots?
Boxxo!
I won first place!
And I'm going to eat time! Pass out!
Congratulations!
But something's come up that we
should do before we celebrate.
Why, how do you do, Miss Sawari?
My name's Heavy.
It's nice to meet you.
I accompany Boxxo in his
travels hunting monsters
and exploring the dungeon with the others.
Thank you for your courtesy and decorum.
My name's Sawari, nice to meet you.
With all that out of the way,
tell me, what may I do for you?
Well, I'd like to ask about the boots
you provided for the first place prize.
Lamas, would you please show them to us?
Of course, here.
The shape, size, quality.
Sure enough, there can be no mistake.
Is my suspicion correct that
these are the untiring god's feet?
My, you're a real footwear connoisseur.
They are one of the
masterpieces of Logdium,
a master craftsman renowned
for their shoemaking skills.
Yes, just as I thought.
If I may, I should like to inquire
where you obtained these boots.
Sure, we'd be happy to share. Yes, ma 'am.
Your father said that he
procured those boots during
one of his trips to the
Scorching Sand Stratum.
I recall him being rather elated, as
they were a considerably rare find.
Ah, I see.
The Scorching Sand Stratum, you say.
Thank you very much for your answer.
Are you all right?
I sold lots of alcohol at last
night's Grand Prix wrap party.
Soup with basket clams
will be in demand today.
Boxo! It's Heavy!
Have you seen Heavy today?
Shui's desperate cries seemed
to signal that our brief
time of fun and leisure
had come to an abrupt end.